The resulting what?
What was he going to say?
I don't know actually.
I don't remember.
I have to go watch it now.
So that's just a
video showing you
what I just showed you,
which is that that's yet
another way of engineering
the properties of glass,
and there are so many more.
One of the points I
want to make today
about how to engineer
glass-- so we're talking
about how to change this curve.
Maybe we change the
viscosity by adding O2
which changes the curve here.
Maybe we change
the cooling rate.
Maybe I can use additives,
ions in different ways.
But it turns out
that we have come
to a place where we can
engineer every single one
of these properties.
We can make conducting glass,
even though it's usually
been and usually is insulating.
We can make chemically
active glass.
As you just saw, we can change
the mechanical properties.
There are now flexible
rolls of glass
that look literally like Saran
wrap almost, but they're glass.
And so it all comes
down to the pasta.
And so where we are, if
we use the pasta analogy--
which as you, I think, can
understand I really like
because I really like pasta.
This is a great
analogy for glass
because it's like
in the Roman time,
all we had was one
sauce, everything.
Just mix it all in--
meatballs, pesto,
red sauce, carbonara.
I can go on.
And that's all they did.
They just didn't know why
things were happening.
But now that we know about the
electronic structure of atoms,
we can make glass into any
delicious pasta dish we want,
right?
OK, don't eat it, but
you know what I mean.